Look behind you!
That's it!
You're really getting
carried away, Bulots.
What's going on
between you and Kenzo in your fanfic?
You were kidnapped by gang members,
and then he rescued you.
But the thing is,
he got shot.
Janine, run now!
Instead, you ran straight to him.
Kenzo! Kenzo, my love!
Are you okay, my love?
Kenzo! Oh my god!
You really like making a scene, huh?
You're thinking too far ahead.
I'm just on Chapter 14.
You're already spoiling my ending, huh?
The only ending I know is
Attorney Mendes glaring at you
because you're more focused on your fanfic
than on studying.
Really?
How do I stay awake?
Like this.
Like this?
Huh?
Your breath smells bad.
Why did you buy so much chewing gum?
There are lucky Mint 2 Be wrappers
containing tickets
to an intimate fan meet
with my dear Kenzo.
I need to win one.
You're being delusional again.
Why do you care?
As long as it's for my Kenzo,
yes.
There you go.
Just sleep it off.
After all, you and Kenzo
only see each other in your dreams.
Whoa.
You're a hater now?
Hey! My phone!
It's yours.
Thanks.
How's the story for you, Pip?
EVEN AS THE RAIN POURS HEAVILY,
I CAN STILL HEAR MY HEART BEATING.
I WORRY ABOUT YOU.
It's fine.
But why does it always have to be raining?
Duh!
It's more romantic that way!
There's got to be
those rainy effects there!
It's not very romantic when you end
up with a cold and a fever, right?
You know what? You talk too much.
I'm ignoring you,
your bad looks,
and your bad breath!
I'm also ignoring those without abs,
the single since birth!
And last of all…
I'm ignoring the haters.
I'm going to sleep.
You'd better turn the lights out.
Just go for it, you losers!
Gosh! You're unbelievable!
Just do it already!
- Hey, you're here.
- You're loud. Know what time it is?
Let me guess.
You just came from Janine's, didn't you?
Oh great. It's like I don't even have
a roommate anymore!
Of course I was…
Wait!
Otep.
Damn it!
Sorry.
What were you saying?
As I said, I promised Aunt Marissa
that I'd make sure Janine is safe.
Talk about strict surveillance.
So now we keep on chewing for her,
and all we get is "better luck next time"?
Hey!
- Oh man! I'm telling you!
- Otep, stop it.
I'm telling you!
You will like it.
What is it?
Time to give up, man.
Janine's just not into you.
One more.
There might be something in here.
Oh!
Wait. This is it, man. This is the one!
- Let me see.
- Is this what it looks like?
What does it say?
You look like a fool.
Whatever.
Looking at her first photo
on this dating app, it's a no.
Love to parties?
Is this Otep?
Wrong grammar.
And this one…
Yikes! Her biceps are bigger than yours.
She's like the Incredible Hulk.
- You'll end up getting beaten by her.
- We hope you can donate.
- And be a lifesaver today.
- This one will beat you up.
- Thank you.
- All right. Thank you.
I've been talking,
but you're not listening to me!
It turns out
I don't have anyone beside me.
Is this for the blood donation drive?
Here, this one, 25 years old.
Just a bit older than you,
but this one already has
a fully developed frontal lobe.
"Board Member, Guardians of Humanity."
"My causes and communities…"
"Volunteering and human rights…"
So corny!
- She's too full of herself.
- Don't!
Why?
I thought you didn't like dating apps.
Why bother regretting it?
She's too pretentious.
She's a member of
a volunteer organization I want to join.
And you immediately
called her pretentious?
The problem is
your profile picture is ugly.
That's why nobody swipes right.
I'll change it
to one where you look
like you actually showered.
You're unbelievable.
Not my photo gallery!
Why?
Are you hiding something from me?
- What?
- A scandal.
Hey!
Hey! I already saw that.
- Come on--
- I've already seen that.
I've already seen that.
- Don't be loud.
- Ouch!
Why? Do you have a scandal?
Give me that.
Why do you have this photo of me?
It's so ugly!
- Delete that.
- But it's cute.
Delete it already.
No.
I'm going to upload this on your birthday.
Here's another one.
You know,
let's just look
for someone here on campus.
It looks like you really need
an organic encounter.
How about that one?
Try to have some subtlety.
Fine, never mind.
That one is an irregular student
in our PE class.
Her breath probably smells
worse than yours.
You can't be both stinky.
You really have no filter
on your mouth, do you?
How about that one?
- Miss, calm down.
- What happened?
You're hopeless.
Bulots.
Any dissenting opinion or opinions?
Attorney?
Yes?
I think Janine has one.
All right, Ms. Mesina, let's hear it.
- Let's go.
- Damn you.
The Writ of Kalikasan is…
Is a protection…
Is…
I'm sorry, Attorney.
I'm sorry.
Ms. Mesina, this is just an intro to law.
But when you proceed to law school,
the bar will be higher for you.
And just because you're my goddaughter
doesn't mean you get special treatment.
Attorney Mesina will be so disappointed.
Reminder, everyone.
The 20 cases assigned for you
to read and make case digests of…
No AI.
That's it for today.
Class dismissed.
Is it your first time donating blood?
You know, it helps to listen to music.
Sir, are you okay?
"I expected more from you!"
Good grief!
Tone down the pressure a bit.
What do they expect?
That I had memorized the entire
1987 Constitution already?
I'm struggling enough as it is
with just the preamble.
What's so funny? Is that funny?
I'll punch your jaw.
- Bulots.
- What?
Let's pretend it's your birthday today.
But it's not my birthday yet.
I said let's pretend.
Oh, what should I do?
Who do you want to see?
Of course…
Kenzo baby.
Love that.
Why did you ask?
What is this?
Grand Kenzo Day?
Ouch!
Hey!
Why?
What happened to you?
I donated blood earlier.
Hey.
Look at you go, girl.
You didn't collapse from the needle?
Not really.
I just thought about the thing…
The thing that calms me down.
You're so random.
Thank you.
You'll accompany me in commuting, right?
Do I even have a choice?
Thank you, Besh.
Love you.
I'm finally going to see Kenzo.
Ma?
Wait a second.
Ma.
Your godmother called.
What?
She reported me to you?
Huh?
Report what?
Oh, nothing.
What did she say?
She's inviting us for dinner.
Maybe after your birthday?
Maybe she wants
to train you at her law firm.
You probably impressed her.
Yes, Ma.
She was very impressed with me.
Anyway, why are you still up?
Just some late-night reading.
Once you enter law school next year,
you practically won't be sleeping anymore.
So while you still can,
you'd better sleep!
Okay, Ma.
I'm going to sleep now.
Okay, good.
Say hi to RR.
I love you.
Love you too, Ma.
Okay.
Push.
I need to be careful now.
I know too much.
They won't leave me alone.
Morning or night.
Rain or shine.
But even if it's dangerous,
Kenzo is always there.
Shit!
My nose is stuffed up.
You can keep it.
Why are you always getting yourself
caught in the rain?
Because it takes you so long
to share your umbrella with me.
Good Lord, Janine!
Is that really your answer?
Let the earth swallow me whole, please.
I've got you.
Just don't tell anyone who I really am.
That you're the Undercover Love--
Be quiet about it.
So this is what it's like to have
an action hero for a boyfriend.
As if! Boyfriend already?
Let's calm down first!
As long as I'm here…
I'll take care of you.
You're stinky, Pip.
Is it full already?
I'm in a hurry.
Take my seat, ma'am.
- Thank you, young man.
- No problem, ma'am.
Thank you.
Are you trying to kill me?
It was her.
Was it really her? No way.
Did all of these people chew that gum?
- Of course. That's how much we love Kenzo.
- You're next.
Hello.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- So sorry.
- Are you okay here?
I'm okay now.
- I've got it.
- Hey.
What?
Huh?
Did you forget something?
Of course not.
It's impossible for me to forget this.
- Enjoy.
- Take care, okay?
Thank you.
Let's give Kenzo a round of applause.
We can't hear you!
Louder!
Here! Louder!
Cheer louder! Louder!
- Come on! Shout louder!
- Kenzo!
Louder! Make some noise!
- Come on, that's it! Kenzo's on his way!
Everyone, let's go!
Oh no. It's past 1:00 p.m.
Unbelievable. He's still not here.
You know, ever since he stopped
collaborating with Ashley,
Kenzo has become so unprofessional.
That's true.
It was really Ashley who carried Ash-Zo.
Kenzo is not unprofessional.
You Ash-Zo shippers,
your ship name really suits you.
All you do is bark.
Woof this, woof that.
You aren't even real Kenzo fans.
Excuse me.
We are real Kenzo fans.
Surely we're allowed to complain, right?
Because he's late.
Complain?
Why?
Did he complain to you when only ten of us
streamed his first song?
When only five of us
were watching his IG live,
did he complain to you?
No, right?
Because you don't know him,
and you don't know what he's been through.
The girl is delusional.
What did you say?
Hey, that's enough!
Everybody, calm down.
Why are you calling?
My interview is about to start.
Just talk to me. I'm bored.
Anyway, I have some gossip.
Earlier, I got into a fight
with two of Kenzo's bashers.
So annoying!
And there's a PWD here who's faking it.
Probably just to get Kenzo's attention.
Hey.
He might hear you.
And you know what?
There's a mascot here.
I really feel like this is Kenzo.
You know me.
I have a strong feeling
about these things.
You're actually quite insensitive.
Huh? What was that?
Nothing.
I said you're beautiful, just deaf.
I know I'm beautiful. All right, fine.
Whatever. Bye. Love you.
Love you.
I really feel this is Kenzo.
Hi.
Kenzo?
Is that you?
You don't have to say anything.
It's just us here.
I know you won't let your fans down.
Right?
Can I take a peek?
Just a little.
I'll just peek. Just a little bit.
Sorry, sir. Sorry.
Sorry.
Good afternoon, Mr. Velasco.
Good afternoon, sir.
I'm volunteering
for Guardians of Humanity.
Can you hear me, Mr. Velasco?
Sir?
Mr. Velasco?
Sir, good af…
Damn.
Wow, this excitement is something else.
You're all so strong,
so beautiful, and so handsome.
Wow.
I'm so sorry.
Kenzo won't be able to attend.
Huh?
An emergency just came up.
But he sends his apologies,
blessings, and all sorts of positivity.
Yes, but for now, we need to leave. Yes.
- The heck?
- Let's all stand up.
- My butt is hurting.
- It's okay.
- What the…
- What a waste.
- We've already turned off the aircon.
- I knew it!
- You liar.
- You all need to leave.
Please hurry up.
I still have a date.
You waited for hours,
and then he didn't even show up.
Just unstan him already.
You seem angrier than me.
I was the one who waited.
Hey, I waited too.
I waited for you, you know.
Hey, don't "hey" me.
I didn't tell you to wait.
I'm willing to wait
even if you don't say so.
- You know that.
- I'm also willing to wait for Kenzo.
Even if he doesn't say so.
But that was still wrong, wasn't it?
He made you wait for several hours.
If it were me,
I wouldn't do that.
You already know that, don't you?
When I was in high school,
and now that I'm in college,
Kenzo and his music
were the only ones there to comfort me
because we're both hiding in the shadows
of our more famous parents.
I can relate to that too.
I'm like a shadow following you.
- Huh?
Nothing. I said…
He doesn't even know how you feel.
He doesn't even know you exist.
That's just one-way, Bulots, okay?
Okay, okay.
Anyway, my only wish
for my birthday is that
someday,
he'll know that I exist.
Even if he just reads my fanfic.
Pip.
Sleep here, okay?
Hi, guys!
Long time no see.
Okay.
Let's read some comments first.
"Idol,
please read #MyUndercoverLove
by diehard Kenzonatic fan."
"Written by
TurtleLoverr06."
Wow!
"Best fanfic ever!"
From…
RawrRawr?
Shout out to you, RawrRawr!
And of course,
shout out to you too, TurtleLoverr06.
Actually, I think I can share it here
so that other fans can read it too.
There.
Okay.
Just let me know if TurtleLoverr06's
My Undercover Love
is any good.
Hi TurtleLover06, I just read your fanfic.
I enjoyed it so much.
Maybe we can have dinner soon.
What the heck, Bulots?
What's happening?
I'm viral!
My fanfic!
It's viral now!
And Kenzo messaged me!
Oh my god!
Let's go out! My treat.
Come on!
Damn it. I'm late.
Wait!
Bulots.
Don't I always support you
in everything you do?
Remember the volunteer program?
The one that rejected me?
They have a new opening.
They're looking for volunteers
to train abroad.
Abroad?
What do you mean "mmm"?
They said I just need to attend
that emergency response training course.
And one of the requirements
is a recommendation letter
from a university representative.
Aren't you in the Student Council?
Maybe you could help out.
You're my favorite writer after all.
Just a letter?
All right.
I'll help you,
but on one condition.
What?
Please don't call me Bulots
in front of Kenzo.
Please.
But it's so cute.
Kenzo?
KenBul.
KenBul?
KenkenBul.
Don't you dare embarrass me!
I won't write you the letter.
But it's good.
Kenzo.
KenkenBul.
TurtleLoverr06.
I told you.
Just call me Janine.
Kenzo.
Janine.
- Nice to meet you.
Kenzo, man.
RR.
Nice to meet you.
You're late.
His hand is wet.
And here's the deconstructed
sweet potato reduced to a foam.
Enjoy.
Is there no real food here?
Good thing I already ate.
Anyways, Janine.
The reason I wanted to meet with you
is that my management
is thinking about various projects.
And I told them that
I wanted to collaborate with a fan.
I am your number one fan.
Hey, Bulots.
That's a bit harsh.
Bulots?
Your nicknames for each other are so cute.
- Why Bulots?
- Because--
Short for…
"beauty lots."
Lots of beauty.
That's all. Just being beautiful.
I'm really beautiful, right? Right, Pip?
Pip?
Why Pip?
Because you're the fifth
among your siblings?
Am I right?
Pip, because you were 15 minutes late.
Or it could be 50-50.
50-50 on whether you'd show up or not.
Please bear with my best friend here.
He's quite the joker.
Nice.
You're really good.
Wait, best friend.
Did I hear that right?
I thought you were--
A couple?
No.
Just best friends.
Excuse me.
Salmon at the center.
What we need is a celebration of things
that are often overlooked.
Things that are
often forgotten or unnoticed.
Green peas.
It's green peas reimagined,
reinvented, reborn.
Enjoy.
You know,
out of all the chef's dishes,
this is my favorite.
Thank you.
Thank you, Chef.
Are you okay? Any allergies?
- Chef--
- None.
I eat everything.
That's good. I'm excited. Please try.
Come on, Janine. Try it.
Bulots.
He told me to try it.
You like it?
- Is it good?
- It's delicious.
- Right?
- So delicious.
You know very well
that you're allergic to green peas.
And yet you still ate the dish.
Ouch!
So…
what's the deal with Kenzo, really?
You know what?
You are such a killjoy.
You know, being a fan,
just the right amount is fine.
There's also the risk…
that you're just getting your hopes up.
It's just a fantasy.
But…
what's wrong with hoping?
Hoping hurts.
Waiting hurts.
Well…
What if?
- What if?
- What if…
That 'what if' is dangerous.
Because sometimes…
what you want is right in front of you…
and you don't even notice.
If it's always there anyway,
surely it's not wrong
to dream of something else.
Well, if that's the case,
then it's not wrong to look at others.
No.
Not me, though. I'm strictly for Kenzo.
What?
Why? You're pursuing someone, aren't you?
Look at you.
You're hiding something from me.
She'd better be more beautiful than I am.
Here, take your medicine.
Try eating those green peas again.
Fine, then take care of me again.
RR.
Janine is mine.
I am your rival.
Man.
Not me.
You're just as annoying.
What rival?
Janine said it herself, right?
That it's just a fantasy. Admiration.
Like that. Delusion.
Admit it.
Even if it's out of reach…
Right? Kenzo makes you nervous.
Stand up straight.
Pull up your t-shirt.
Ouch! Look.
Are you going to get through there?
You're really so cute.
Look at that.
Look at me.
- Wow, huh. You're handsome.
- Right?
- Wow.
- Of course.
Hey, man.
I'm not the one with a celebrity rival.
Look.
Look at those abs.
Are those all yours?
It looks like you have extra food there.
You're ugly, Otep.
Go take a bath.
Hey, I do take a bath, first of all.
I take a bath.
Go ahead, flex. There.
Look.
Look at it.
- Man, I'm not that far off.
- You look like a fool.
We matched on the app,
but you didn't reply.
No, it's just…
No need to explain.
This is the first time I've seen you here.
Is it your first time here?
No.
I'm athletic.
Before.
I was also a swimmer
back in elementary school.
I didn't say anything.
Is this for self-improvement?
Or are you trying to impress someone?
Do you want me to teach you proper form?
Just follow my lead.
- Okay.
You have to hinge your hips.
Then when you stand up,
squeeze your glutes.
Okay?
What are glutes?
Your butt.
Go.
Let me see.
Like this.
Okay, wait.
Engage your core.
Yes. Okay, try it.
One, two, three.
Squeeze your glutes.
Yes.
Good.
Bulots.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to work out.
Why? Do you own this place?
How did you know I'm here?
Otep told me.
What's your deal?
Trying to impress someone, huh?
Turtleloverr06?
Hi! Can we take a picture?
How did you recognize me?
I follow you. You're famous now.
Is it okay?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Ms. Sue?
- Hi, Ms. Sue.
- Hey.
Take more shots.
- Thank you.
- Can we take a photo?
- Yes, come on.
I read your bestselling book
on environmental activism!
Wow, you're so inspiring.
Sure.
There! One more!
Yes, one more!
Oh, one minute.
You can do it.
Kenzo?
Hello, Kenzo?
Janine, are you free on Thursday?
There's an advance screening
of my mom's movie.
It's just for
my closest friends and family.
Can you be there?
Closest friends and family?
Is that a yes?
Yes, yes, yes, of course!
- Bulots! What?
- I'll go.
- Good night. See you.
- That's five minutes already.
- Bye, Kenzo.
- Bye, Janine.
What?
One more set. You can do it. Come on.
Let me help you.
Ouch.
Sorry.
Sorry, Besh.
Lift this.
There.
It's hard.
Hey, you'd better not mess with me.
- I even dressed up.
- Careful.
There. Okay, sit down.
Sit down.
Wait.
You're taking so long!
Should I remove it?
- Hey, don't mess with me.
- Wait.
Okay.
Happy birthday, Bulots.
Wow. Thank you.
- Okay.
- Let me make a wish first.
Okay, go, go.
Nice!
Okay.
- I should be the first one to greet you.
- Wow.
You jerk!
You're crazy. It's my birthday!
I look so ugly here!
It's fine.
It's cute. I told you.
Yeah, right!
But, Bulots…
That's not my gift yet.
What else?
Yeah, I still have a surprise. Thursday.
Thursday?
Why?
Kenzo invited me to a special
block screening of his mom's movie.
But that's at 7 p.m.
So around nine,
I can still catch your surprise.
And why does it have to be Thursday?
Why not today?
Thursday is the only day allowed.
Allowed by who?
Just trust me. You'll like it.
It's our special place.
- Our special place.
- Yeah.
I know what it is.
Where?
In Mrs. Helga's room.
Where you took a dump.
That's your special place, right?
- Crap.
- Crap. That's where you…
Oh crap.
- There. You look like crap.
- Oh really?
Huh?
Good thing it's your birthday.
- Don't!
- Huh?
- It's my birthday.
- Don't!
You're going to refuse me?
- Okay.
- Close your eyes.
Are you ready?
Bulots, okay?
Smile!
- Wow!
- Happy birthday.
Happy birthday to me.
Yes, Pip.
This will be quick. Promise.
Okay. Take care, Bulots, okay?
All right. Bye-bye.
- Okay, no problem.
- We understand. Thank you!
- Thank you.
- Where are we going to eat?
Hello, hello, everyone!
Wow! Her life has already changed.
Anyway, as I was saying…
Today will be life-changing.
So let's just wait a bit.
But we promise this will be
worth your while. All right?
So, let's just wait for a little while
because we promise
it's going to be worth your time.
Miss!
Can you help me?
Which one is better for you? This one or…
Just wear that. Here, put it on.
- Are you sure this is better?
- Yes.
Let me see. Face me. There.
You look so handsome.
- Is it okay now?
- Good luck!
Our next performer
is a record-breaking contemporary movement
piece artist of her generation.
The one and only…
Kropek.
Because you deserve the best,
we feel you also deserve
an opening prayer.
Let us all stand.
In the name of the Father…
The Son…
- The Holy Spirit.
- Amen.
One more?
- One more.
- Okay.
This gathering is truly very special
because we have a dialogue.
We have the cast and director,
Pascal Seswa,
veteran actor Joel Saracho,
Sheryl Diamante, and Celeste De Guia.
So yes, does anyone have questions
for our very exciting cast?
Oh, yes.
You in pink who looks like Gen Z.
Yes.
What time does it start?
I'm just very, very excited.
Aww, that's so sweet. She's just excited.
After this, it will start
and you'll truly experience
the movie in its full glory.
All five hours of it.
Five hours?
Five hours, yes.
Are you still there?
The movie is five hours long. Damn. Sorry.
- Miss!
- Oh, Ma'am Sue.
Ma'am, sorry.
We're closed right now
for a private event.
Just two bottles, please.
- Please, miss.
- Two bottles?
But, ma'am…
Please!
Hey!
Oh!
You look like
you're dressed up for church.
Why are you all dressed up?
Oh.
And you're at a local diner.
May I?
Sure.
So, either A,
you got dumped.
B,
you got stood up, right?
Letter B.
Final answer.
But why here?
Why here?
Because this is
where I first realized that…
That…
That I love her.
The girl from the gym?
Okay.
- When we had problems--
- Here you go, sir.
- One bucket.
- Thank you, miss.
When we had family problems,
she brought me here.
Did she give you advice?
No.
She just kept making me laugh all night.
Even if her jokes were corny,
she really got me.
I even forgot I had problems back then.
Okay.
Here.
What's that?
I carved this when she fell asleep.
I carved it because I didn't want
to forget that night.
I didn't want to forget
the moment I found the person
who would make me happy.
Miss. Hey. It's over.
Oh, it's already over.
It's already 2 a.m.
Oh no!
- Excuse me, please. Sorry.
- Wait!
- Cheers.
Hey, RR, think about
what I told you earlier.
We need volunteers at the Fire Department.
I feel cold.
Oh. Here.
Good thing I'm prepared.
Thank you.
Hey!
There's your best friend.
Hello.
Pip.
I feel cold too, you know.
Take it.
Sue.
That's hers.
Okay. Go, go, go.
Go.
It's really cold.
Gym expert, right?
Slash.
Environmental activist.
Published author.
And slash.
You seem to have it all, huh?
Right, Pip?
By the way, this is Sue.
- And this is Janine.
- Hi.
Nice to meet you.
Pip? Why do you call him Pip?
Isn't his name RR?
They thought I was mute
back in elementary.
Can I call you Pip too?
- Sure!
- No!
Hey!
I'm the only one
who can call you that, right?
That's just ours.
Anyways…
I was inviting RR
to join me in the BFP volunteer program.
BFP?
Firefighter?
That's dangerous.
And hey.
Didn't you tell me
you'd focus on your midterms?
As for my organization,
they send volunteers to Sudan.
- Sudan?
- Yes.
That would be good training for RR.
Yeah.
You're a member of
Guardians of Humanity, right?
Not just a member.
One of the Board of Directors.
No wonder I'm so bored with you now.
Huh?
How about your studies?
That's a good opportunity for RR.
We need someone who's as passionate as RR.
Passionate?
Why?
Are you lifelong friends?
Do you have childhood memories together?
Hey.
You just met.
- Hey.
- His studies won't stop.
I mean, it will only just take one year,
and then I think
he will do so good there.
Anyways, RR told me.
You watched the special screening
of the new Pascal Seswa film.
- I'm such a fan!
- Yes!
And you know, Kenzo was really sweet.
Kenzo?
He even invited me to dinner
after we watched the movie.
Dinner?
It's almost three o'clock!
Oh, I mean,
midnight snack!
Or maybe breakfast.
Just pick which one you like.
Good thing you didn't have an allergy.
No, I didn't.
Because there were paramedics
on standby for me.
That's how sweet he is.
That's so nice!
So nice, right?
- That's so nice! Wow!
- Oh my god!
- It's really nice!
- It's so nice!
It's really nice!
- So nice!
- Nice!
- Right? It's really nice!
So? Is she your girlfriend now?
I just met her.
How can she be my girlfriend?
Is there a chance?
We do.
Were you there all night?
Yes.
Why do you have so many questions?
Is it wrong to be curious
about my best friend's future partner?
She's mature.
I'll give her that.
Maybe that's what you need.
You're right.
She's mature.
Unlike you, who's very immature.
What are you doing?
Why?
Can't I be sweet with my best friend?
Are you afraid you might lose me
because of her?
That I'll lose time for you?
Killjoy.
But yes,
as selfish as it may sound.
Good thing you know.
You're very selfish.
At least now you know my favorite seafood.
Huh?
Shellfish!
You're corny.
Yeah, idiot.
You're smiling.
Your nostrils are flaring.
Pip.
Come study with me, okay?
Where are you?
I'm doing volunteer work with the BFP.
It's better without one.
Why does her lover have two Rs?
Is it just a style
or does it have a meaning?
Where is the next part?
Waiting for the next chapter!
I'll name my kid after Kenzo.
Hey, Janine, about last night.
Really sorry.
Don't worry. I really liked the movie.
So it's okay.
Chapter 31.
Kenzo promised I'd be safe
as long as he's there.
But why does it feel like this?
It's like something inside me has changed.
Even though I know Kenzo is there,
it feels like I'm looking
for someone else.
There's someone else
I want to see.
Someone familiar?
I feel weak.
I'm getting dizzy.
Poison?
Did they poison my water?
Kenzo?
Pip?
Ken…
Sis, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Okay.
Does this sulking of yours have something
to do with the loss of your shadow?
Because if you don't like him, it's okay.
Like if you turned him down,
what do you call that?
Rejected?
How can I reject him
when he didn't even court me?
So dramatic.
Okay, so he's moving on from you.
How can he move on
when we were never together?
You don't have to be exes
to move on from someone.
Why? Is he courting someone else?
What are you even saying, Jess?
Okay.
Because you guys are so, so close.
And I get that, okay?
Like he's always there.
But sometimes,
you just need to take a step back.
So that you can really see him.
Because you only get to see him now
because he's slowly walking away.
But if I were you,
I wouldn't even let him walk any further.
Because before you know it, he'll be gone.
He'll be so far away.
So, so far away.
So far away?
So far away.
Pip, when is the BFP training?
You're into boxing now?
- Yeah.
- Isn't it in QC?
Really? So you're doing it regularly?
Hi!
I'm happy you decided to join us, Janine.
Are we close?
Huh?
Nothing. I said…
I'm happy to be here.
That's nice.
Hasn't it started yet?
Hold this.
Let's go! Let's start!
- Hey! This is embarrassing!
- Come on!
Come on!
Do you need help with your visa?
Visa for where?
Okay. Next!
- Next. Okay.
- Next!
Pip,
what is the visa for?
For our volunteer work in Sudan.
Left.
This is a major life decision.
And no one's going to tell me?
He's an injured person, Janine.
He can't talk to you.
Left.
He'll really get injured
if he doesn't answer me.
- This is embarrassing!
- Left.
Right!
Left!
Just stay steady, okay?
We're almost there, Pip.
Pip?
Pip? Really?
I'm the only one allowed to call you that.
Focus, Janine.
Janine?
What, you don't want
to call me Bulots anymore?
Before, you didn't want
to be called Bulots.
Now you want it?
You're confusing, sis.
Sis?
There were other people before.
It's different
because your Kenzo wasn't there.
So you're getting back at me?
Why would I get back at you?
- You're a mess.
- Whatever.
No one else can call you Pip.
Let's go, Pip and friend!
Damn it! Janine!
- Stop it!
- What's your problem?
Stop!
- Janine!
- What?
What's going on with you?
Okay.
Sorry, sir.
It's all right.
You know that…
“Pip” is ours.
Wait.
Why does it feel like
you're the one sulking?
Shouldn't it be me?
Because you didn't even tell me
you're really going to Sudan.
I'm your best friend.
Let me remind you of that.
I'm still just applying.
I'm not even sure yet.
A lot can still happen.
Are you really ready?
Have you completed your training?
Do you know how to speak their language?
What do you call it?
Sudanians?
Sudanese?
Oh.
What if someone asks for help?
As a first responder, what will you do?
Sorry.
How can I help?
No English!
No, no, no! No English!
What happened, madam? How can I help?
Are you stupid?
They don't know how to speak English.
Just say what you want to say.
If you don't want me to leave,
just say it.
I'm just making sure
you're really ready to leave.
You seem so eager.
What if someone drowns?
Do you know how to do CPR?
Madam!
Call emergency services! Right away!
You're really stupid, huh?
I said they don't know
how to speak English!
Madam!
Here, idiot. Here.
Here.
Sorry.
Sorry too.
- For what?
Pip?
Why don't you just sleep here?
It's cold.
Excuse me.
Are you sleepy?
Not yet.
I don't know what happened
after I lost consciousness.
All I know is…
I just woke up,
and Kenzo was already with me.
Relax.
Once again,
he saved me.
Looks like you drank a strong poison.
You are calling me by a different name.
Thank you.
You have saved my life many times.
Didn't I tell you that
as long as I'm here,
you are safe?
Wait, what's happening?
Oh my gosh.
I've been waiting for this my whole life.
But why does it feel like this?
Something feels wrong.
Isn't this supposed to be my fantasy?
Sorry, Kenzo.
I'm sorry.
Why?
I don't know, okay?
But one thing I'm sure of
is that every time I close my eyes,
it's not you that I see.
Who do you see?
Prepared breakfast for you.
I went ahead. I still have a makeup class.
Oh damn!
Oh!
I thought you left.
Couldn't I have just taken a shower first?
Don't you have water at your place?
You should eat. Go eat.
Eat already!
I prepared that. I know you're hungry.
Aren't you going to eat?
Later.
Fine, don't. You're so fussy.
Hey, RR.
I'm reminding you about your interview
with our head of volunteers.
Don't forget!
Why do you care if the one I see now
is RR and not Kenzo?
Huh?
Sis, you're so out of it again!
Okay, are you even done
reading all of your cases
or writing any of your case digests?
This is so unlike you!
And you've had so many absences already!
What's happening?
Nothing.
Maybe I'm just a bit out of focus lately.
Does this have something to do
with your shadow?
Shadow?
Shadow.
Here it is!
What?
What? You're so dramatic!
We already kissed.
You kissed?
Hey! You're so loud!
Whatever.
So did he kiss you? Did you kiss him?
- Does that even matter?
- Yeah, of course!
So are you guys official now?
Yeah, kind of like some situation…
Situationship?
Oh no.
Something happened earlier.
Something already happened?
Okay, your shadow is moving fast.
You're crazy!
I mean…
That annoying Sue sent a message again.
It looks like
they're really going to Sudan.
Then tell him not to go.
Why would I do that? That's RR's dream.
Yes, but how about you?
How about you guys?
Why would I make him choose?
Then don't make him choose.
The best you can do
is convince him
before anything is too late.
Come on!
Come on.
Good thing
you didn't get caught in the rain.
Come back again.
Did RR tell you that
this place is very important to us?
Are you guilt-tripping me, Janine?
So I'll tell RR
not to go through with it?
You don't want to lose him
because you need him?
I don't want him to leave
because I know he won't be happy there.
He just wants to prove something.
That's why he's doing that volunteer work.
But I know he won't be happy there.
Why?
Because you're not there?
And you think
you're in control of his happiness?
Do you hear
how selfish you sound, Janine?
Yes, I'm selfish.
Stupid.
I know.
I'm stupid because I thought
this time would never come.
The possibility that he would leave.
I admit that was my fault.
But I'm not my mistake, Sue.
I don't want to be defined by my mistake.
You're wrong.
His happiness doesn't depend on me.
My happiness depends on him.
So I'm begging you, Sue.
Please don't take away my happiness.
Janine…
The final decision is his, Janine.
Not mine.
Maybe…
Maybe he'll change his mind.
Please help me, Sue.
Don't let me lose him.
He's all I have.
Pip?
Did Sue tell you anything?
Nothing. Why?
But the person who was supposed
to interview me canceled it.
I don't know.
They said they'll just reschedule.
Maybe that's your sign.
Huh?
Not to go?
We have an outing this weekend.
Huh?
I signed both of us up for tree planting.
Jess's organization.
You signed me up?
Yeah.
Outsiders are allowed here, right?
You can invite Otep.
Who knows?
They might become a couple there.
So dirty here and I'm so tired.
Excuse me.
- I'll help you.
- Sorry.
I don't want your help.
We're not even close.
Wow.
Nice to meet you.
Are you a future law school?
Student.
Future law student.
Wow!
Oh wow!
Smooth! There's a spark!
Another one! There's a spark!
- There's…
- Really? Like that?
There it is!
So sweet!
Oh my!
That's a spark!
There's a spark!
- Right?
- Let's go!
Two already.
- Really?
- Yes.
Don't get so close to me.
Oh my god.
Oh, I didn't mean to.
I didn't mean to.
The soil was so hard. It went like that.
Oh really?
Really?
- I swear I didn't mean it!
- Hey!
You did it on purpose!
- Sorry.
It was hard! It just moved like that!
Like that!
You're so gross!
Bro, you covered me with soil!
- Yeah!
- Now we're both dirty!
- I didn't mean to make you dirty!
- There!
Right!
Hey, I just ate!
Ew!
Wait a minute! Not my face!
- Stop! Stop it!
- I'm sorry!
- You're so fussy!
- Why did I eat it?
- We've leveled up!
- I'm just explaining.
Before, we used to debrief on the rooftop.
Thanks, Bulots.
I realized a lot.
Especially about our passion.
What did you realize?
When…
When you realized you wanted
to take up environmental law,
I figured out what I wanted in my life.
What I should focus on in life.
This.
Helping.
Volunteering.
I didn't immediately figure out
what I wanted.
But now I do.
I won't give this up.
You're lucky.
Because before,
I almost gave up on what I wanted.
Even this opportunity…
I don't want to let it go.
Just because you won't go abroad
doesn't mean you're giving up.
Why don't you just stay, Pip?
A lot of people need you here.
For goodness sake, Ms. Mesina.
AI?
I thought you were
an environmental advocate?
Why did you use AI
to write your case digest?
You're a hypocrite.
And you think I wouldn't detect it? Huh?
This is so embarrassing for you.
Forget about your DL dreams.
Because most likely,
I'll give you a three.
Way below the cutoff.
- Have you tried this?
- Let's try it.
- Let's go here!
- Where?
- Did you have your breakfast?
- So delicious.
- I always come here.
- Try this.
- Sausage? Sweetened pork?
- I'll have sweetened pork.
Hey, RR!
Your best friend left this.
Give it to her, okay?
She was here?
Yes. She was with Sue.
Their steamed pork bun is also good.
- You want?
- The macaroni soup.
Okay. Okay, miss…
Pares mix, please.
Where are you, Pip?
Come see me, please?
For once, can you come
to me instead, Janine?
Pip?
- Pip, I--
- Sorry, Janine.
What's the problem again? Huh?
I don't have a problem.
But I do.
I have a problem with what you did.
Did you really have
to sabotage my application?
For what?
So I wouldn't leave?
I'm sorry, Pip.
I didn't mean
to sabotage your application.
Then what was that? What do you call that?
Just for fun?
Just say you don't want me to leave
because you're afraid
of being left behind.
Yes!
I'm afraid of being left behind.
Sorry!
Instead of apologizing,
maybe you should change, right?
You should have just talked to me directly
instead of doing something behind my back.
After everything we've been through,
you should at least give me that.
Pip.
I've told you many times, right?
Maybe you can just stay.
And how many times have I told you
that it really matters to me?
For my future.
You don't understand that?
Is it so hard to understand
that I want us to stay together?
Fine, for you. Right? It's always you.
It's always you. Always Ja…
Always Janine!
Why is it always you, huh?
When you're sick, who's with you?
When you have a problem,
who solves it for you?
When you have enemies,
who's on your side? Isn't it me?
That's my fault, Pip.
I'm sorry.
Right, Pip? You said I should change
instead of apologizing.
I will. Here it is. I'll change!
Pip… Pip, I'll change.
Please don't leave me, Pip.
I'll do anything for you, Pip.
- Janine.
- Pip.
I wish I'd realized this sooner.
Yeah.
You really should have.
Because damn it! I've loved you all along!
I'm mad at myself
because I want to be mad at you,
but I can't.
Because I know I'll keep coming back.
Whether you like it or not,
my whole life revolves around you.
So please let me walk away now.
No….
- I need to walk away from you now.
- Pip…
Pip, sorry. Please.
I'll do anything, Pip.
Pip. Pip, I'll do anything.
Please don't leave me.
Pip… This isn't supposed
to be our ending, right?
Please don't leave me, Pip.
Pip.
Janine.
I'm not a character in your stories.
This is real life.
In all your stories,
you're always the main character.
Can it be me this time?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry…
Pip.
Mom, I'll come home this weekend.
Ma.
It's okay.
Ma, I failed.
Want to sit down? Let's sit.
I failed school.
I failed RR.
And I failed you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Ma.
Do you know how many times
I almost failed in law school?
Did you think
I didn't struggle with the bar exam?
Have you thought of
how many times I loved
and got hurt before I met your dad?
And how many times we almost
gave up on each other.
How did you endure that, Ma?
I mean…
How do I become like you?
An Attorney Mesina.
My child,
I became who I am
not because I always win
or I'm always right.
I am who I am
because I can move on
when I make mistakes.
And besides,
there's already
an Attorney Marissa Mesina.
You just be Janine Mesina.
Everything is going to be okay.
I'm so proud of you.
Dear Sir/Madam,
I strongly recommend
Mr. Raymond Richard Velasco,
RR.
I can confidently say
that he possesses the hard work,
determination,
and compassion required
for humanitarian work.
To most, he is RR.
But to me,
he is Pip.
I have known him since we were children.
He is selfless,
always putting others before himself.
He would give up what is his
just to help others.
That's the kind of volunteer
that would excel in your organization.
I will miss my Pip.
But the world deserves him too.
His generosity,
his service,
and his humanity.
You?
Bulots?
I know what you're going to say.
As long as I'm here,
they will not stop.
I need to stay away…
for you…
and for me.
I understand.
There are also a lot of people
who need you.
Not just me.
So you're ready to let me go?
Not yet…
because you're forgetting something.
Janine, where are you?
Won't you even say goodbye?
A send-off?
For whom?
For RR.
He's already been called in for training.
It seems things are going well.
There's an opening for trainees.
He's highly recommended by someone.
Really?
Wait.
When is he leaving?
Tonight.
What?
Miss, this is a holdup.
Give me your things.
My boyfriend's flight is today.
What are you talking about?
Are you crazy? Give me your things.
Your cellphone too.
Give it to me.
Driver, stop the vehicle!
How selfish!
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry if I was being too selfish.
I'm sorry if I got scared.
But you could have at least
let me say goodbye to you.
Pip, I love you so much!
I love you so much, Pip.
Can you please repeat what you said?
I didn't hear everything that you said.
From the top, please.
Also, why do you writers
think rain is romantic?
Even though you'll just end up
with a cold or fever after that.
Pip!
Here's your umbrella.
You left it at the eatery the other day.
Pip.
It's okay if you want to leave.
You don't have to stay just for me.
After all the trouble you caused,
you're just going to make me leave anyway?
No.
Bulots…
When did I leave
without saying goodbye to you?
I'm serious.
It's real life now.
Whatever makes you happy.
It's only for a moment anyway.
We can do it, right?
After all the time we've been together,
just like I told you,
I'll always come back to you.
You're really annoying.
You look so handsome when you smile.
Hey!
Aren't you going to compliment me too?
Am I ugly?
I already said you're handsome.
I'm waiting for you to say I'm beautiful.
You don't find me beautiful anymore
ever since you met that girl?
Why are you smiling? You're leaving and…
Take one.
Sorry.
Wait.
Your delivery was bad.
You might wake up.
Try it.
- Thank you.
Hey!
- Try it.
- Answer.
- Cut!
- Damn it. Why is it like that?
Look at your chest.
There. Position your chest.
Adjust your chest.
Okay, go on. Do it. Show me.
Like that.
I don't believe it.
Do it.
- I have a question.
- You know, Janine, I'm not in the mood.
How do you make a red egg?
Scratch it.
You're corny.
You look so handsome when you smile.
Kenzo is calling.
On my IG.
So, how's my hair?
Hi, Turtleloverr06!
Hello.
I read your fanfic, My Undercover Love.
Huh?
I really liked it.
Really? Shit! Oh!
I wasn't cursing at you.
Damn!
Director, he's drooling!